[
    {
        "title": "Name the Year"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Name the year that the pound note was finally withdrawn from circulation.",
        "answer": "1984"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Name the year when food rationing ended when restrictions on the sale of meat was lifted (one year either way).",
        "answer": "1954"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "In what year was Prince Harry born?",
        "answer": "1984"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "In what year was Maradonaâ€™s Hand of God goal in the World Cup?",
        "answer": "1986"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Name the year when Michael Jackson died.",
        "answer": "2009"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "In what year was the Berlin Wall demolished?",
        "answer": "1989"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "In what year was the funeral of Diana, Princess of Wales?",
        "answer": "1997"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Name the year when Hillary and Tenzing reached the summit of Mount Everest.",
        "answer": "1953"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "In what year did Margaret Thatcher become Prime Minister?",
        "answer": "1979"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "In what year was J.R. shot in Dallas?",
        "answer": "1980"
    }
]
